RGS — Revenue and Growth Systems
An evidence-based revenue diagnostic
Built for owner-led trade and field service businesses
We diagnose where revenue is being lost
Across leads, sales, operations, finances, and owner dependence
The scorecard is preliminary and self-reported
Final recommendations require diagnostic review and evidence validation
This is the front door
An owner can complete it in about two minutes
Output: a preliminary 0–1,000 estimate with pillar bands
A starting signal — not a final diagnosis
RGS validates it against evidence before recommending action
Trust framing is built into the surface itself
Behind the scenes: the operating system
Customers move across a lifecycle board
Lead → Diagnostic → Implementation → Ongoing Support
Diagnostic Workspace: case file, intake, sources, uploads, readiness
Implementation Workspace is separate
Revenue Tracker is a separate add-on
Client data is staged: provided, pending review, accepted, follow-up
The next four accounts are synthetic showcase data
They demonstrate the shape of the system end-to-end
Atlas Home Services
Diagnostic structure is complete
But the evidence underneath is thin
Truth-Test readiness: Not Ready
The system refuses to overclaim on weak evidence
Northstar HVAC
Same diagnostic shape
Stronger evidence: interview, connected sources, uploads
Truth-Test readiness: Diagnostic-ready
Confidence improves because the inputs improved
The system rewards real evidence, not assertions
Summit Roofing & Restoration
Evidence crosses the bar for implementation
Findings are sized and prioritized
Each finding is tied to evidence references
Ready to drive an implementation plan
Not just a conversation
Keystone Plumbing Co.
What the system looks like over a quarter
Three drafts: Week 1, Week 4, Week 8
Plus eight weekly check-ins
Recommendations accepted, one rejected by the owner
Outcomes logged at Week 8
AR over 60 days: 14% → 11%
Owner hours per week: 62 → 48
Owner believed crew utilization was 90%
Measured utilization: 72%
The system records the contradiction
These outcomes are synthetic — the shape of a learning loop
When we say a business has a revenue problem
The evidence backs it
Ready for the first real client run